Guide to the Creative Time Archive 1973-2006 MSS.179
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V: Video and Film, 107335
  - Subseries B: Video Recordings - Originals, 107338
    - Art in the Anchorage - John Kelly, 6/22/87, 1987; 107591 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0500)
    - Art on the Beach (opening) - Mark Antrobus, "Mud People", 1987; 107590 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0253)
    - Gretchen Langheld, Creative Time Benefit, 6/30/87, 1987; 107589 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0402)
    - John Torreano, Creative Time Benefit, 6/10/87, 1987; 107588 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0468)
    - Performance in the Park - Clarice Marshall, 1987; 107587 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0289)
    - SRL [Survival Research Laboratories], CNN, 8/13/87 (Filmed at Stanford Conference on Design, July 1987) [Press], 107586 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0596)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Contraband, Evol, 1988; 107585 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0147)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Scott Sherk, Joel Sanders, Ed Tomney, Brigid Kennedy, 1988; 107584 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0209)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera (long shot from front), 1988; 107583 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0207)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, "Piranesi in NY", 1988; 107582 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0195)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, "Piranesi in NY" (complete performance), 1988; 107581 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0211)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, "Piranesi in NY" (NTSC Dub), 1988; 107580 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0213)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, 6/14/88 (ledge, stage left, cut-aways), 1988; 107579 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0404)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, 6/16/88 (3rd row, tight in), 1988; 107578 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0406)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Station House Opera, 6/18/88 (3rd Row Wide Shot), 1988; 107577 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0151)
    - Marcos Kurtycz, "Organikwars" 12/8/88-12/10/88; "Organrites" 12/8/88; "One Dos Tres O!" 12/9/88; "Clavarte" 12/10/88, 1988; 107576 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0458)
    - SRL [Survival Research Laboratories], Shea Stadium 5/19/88; CBS News 5/17/88 [Press], 107575 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0464)
    - Survival Research [Laboratories], [1988]; 107574 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0602)
    - Survival Research Laboratories, [1988]; 107573 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0552)
    - Tony Fisher, Steven Ausbury, "The Lost Opera", 1988; 107572 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0462)
    - Dumb Type, "pH" 1990, "Pleasure Life" 1988, 1988, 1990; 107571 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0540)
    - Merry Conway, Noni Pratt, "As a Dream That Vanishes" 1991; "In the Eye of the Beholder" 1988, 1988, 1991; 107570 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0460)
    - "Desire Borne", 1989; 107569 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0381)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Jessie Jane Lewis, "Blind Ally", 6/22/89, 1989; 107568 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0177)
    - Leni Schwendinger, "Light Site-ings", 11/1/89, 1989; 107567 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0265)
    - Mark Pauline, 1989 Sculpture Grant Award Exhibition, San Francisco Artspace, July 11-Aug 19, 1989 (Dir. Jonathan Reiss and Leslie Asako Gladsjo), 107566 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0600)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Karen Finley, "3 Parables and 2 Testimonies", 9/28/90, 1990; 107565 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0191)
    - HIV TV, Swarthmore College, 12/16/90, 1990; 107564 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0520)
    - John Kelly, "Love of a Poet", 10/19/90, 107563 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0436)
    - Kit-Yin Snyder, Enrico IV Set/Installation - Creative Media Conc., 9/25/90, 1990; 107562 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0434)
    - The Bowery Concert, 9/15/90 (4 PM show), 1990; 107561 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0416)
    - Cai Guo-Qiang, "Explosion Projects", 1990-2002, 107560 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0663)
    - "Clean Needles Save Lives", [1991]; 107559 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0526)
    - "Needle Exchange" (without credits), [1991]; 107558 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0528)
    - Dumb Type, "pH", Kyoto Municipal Museum of the Arts, Institute Contemporary Arts, Nagoya, Spring 1991, 107557 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0536)
    - Dumb Type, "pH", [1991]; 107556 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0538)
    - Dumb Type, "pH", [1991]; 107555 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0542)
    - Fear of Disclosure - Ellen Spiro, Marina Alvarez, "(In)Visible Women", [1991]; 107554 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0444)
    - Jordi Torrent, "Honeymoon", 1991; 107553 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0438)
    - Antoni Miraldi, "Honeymoon Project" (cued for 10 minute viewing segment, parts I and II), [1991]; 107552 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0141)
    - La Fura Dels Baus, "Suz/O/Suz", 4/1/91, 1991; 107551 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0185)
    - "Transitions Inc.", 5/9/92, 1992; 107550 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0440)
    - Fear of Disclosure - Marlon Riggs, "Non, Je Ne Regrette Rien", 1992; 107549 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0446)
    - Fear of Disclosure - Marlon Riggs, "Non, Je Ne Regrette Rien", [1992]; 107548 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0668)
      Duration: [37 min.]
    - Jordi Torrent, "Monuments in Love", 1992; 107547 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0139)
    - Maria Perez, "Safersister" Public Service Announcements (in English and Spanish), [1992]; 107546 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0682)
    - "Patina Du Prey's Memorial Dress", Hunter Reynolds, ICA Boston, 1993; 107545 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0510)
    - "We Interrupt This Program" (Dir. Mary Ellen Strom, Prod. Barbara L. Tsumagari), 1993; 107544 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0674)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - Interviews, 1993; 107543 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0486)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - News All Evening NY 1 6/21/93; News All Morning NY 1 7/30/93; Good Day NY 7/6/93; Daybreak CNN 7/10/93; Channel 9 News 8/2/93; MTV News 8/11/93; NY Views 8/14/93 [Press], 1993; 107542 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0472)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - TV coverage, interviews [Press], 1993; 107541 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0397)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - TV coverage, interviews [Press], 1993; 107540 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0399)
      Duration: [90 min.]
    - 42nd Street Art Project - TV coverage, interviews [Press], 1993; 107539 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0400)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Elizabeth Streb, Dyke TV, Episode 19, 1993; 107538 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0504)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Elizabeth Streb, Ringside, "Kid Action", 1993; 107537 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0243)
    - Debra Levine, "Hairy Tales", [1993]; 107536 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0442)
    - Dyke TV Arts Compilation, 1993; 107535 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0508)
    - Dyke TV, Episodes 1 and 3, 1993; 107534 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0506)
    - Elizabeth Streb, "Ringside" Choreography (excerpts), 1993; 107533 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0681)
    - Glenn Belverio, "Two Spirits Speak Out", 1993; 107532 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0263)
    - Nelson Rodriguez, "HIV: A Home Video" (Draft #2), "13 Years" (Draft #3), "HIV: A Home Video" (Draft #4), 1993; 107531 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0518)
    - Thomas Allen Harris, "Heaven Earth and Hell", 1993; 107530 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0365)
    - Toni Dove, "Mesmer, Secrets of the Human Frame", [1993]; 107529 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0670)
      Duration: [12 min.]
    - 20 Years of Art in Unexpected Places, Dyke TV, 7/94, 1994; 107528 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0357)
    - 20 Years of Art in Unexpected Places, Dyke TV, 7/94, 1994; 107527 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0430)
    - 20th Anniversary celebration (tape 1), 1994; 107526 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0391)
      Format: HI 8
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration (tape 2), 1994; 107525 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0393)
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration, 7/7/94 (tape 1 of 2), 1994; 107524 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0608)
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration, 7/7/94 (tape 2 of 2), 1994; 107523 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0363)
    - 20th Anniversary Celebration, 7/7/94 (tape 3), 1994; 107522 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0395)
    - Anniversary Party Interviews, [1994]; 107521 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0484)
    - 42nd Street Art Project - PBS Video, MacNeil Lehrer News Hour, 9/23/94 [Press], 1994; 107520 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0474)
    - Dyke TV, Best of Winter '94, 1994; 107519 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0516)
    - Martha Wilson, Joyce Scott, Blondell Cummings, Reno, Carnival Knowledge, "Body Politics", 2/14/94, 1994; 107518 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0512)
    - Martha Wilson, Mary Ellen Strom, Peggy Pettitt, Holly Hughes, "Body Politics", 2/15/94, 1994; 107517 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0383)
    - Rebecca Bollinger, "Alphabetically Sorted", 1994; 107516 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0201)
    - Use Mass Transit - Hey Bozo! TV Coverage [Press], [1994]; 107515 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0251)
    - Relax, Fly Mass Transit, 1995; 107514 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0697)
      Format: 5.25" Removable Hard Disk Cartridge
    - Thomas Allen Harris, "Vintage: Families of Value" documentary, 1995; 107513 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0255)
    - VAPP 1995 Application - Gretchen Bender, "Still/Here", "Total Recall"; Ron Kuivila, "VR on $5/Day; Frank Mann, "A Timely Existence"; Grahame Weinbren: "Sonata", "The Erl King", 107512 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0261)
    - Art in the Anchorage - EAR, Harmony Rockets, 1996; 107511 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0215)
    - D.A. Therrien, "Pandaemonium", BBC 1996 [Press], 107510 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0693)
    - Music in the Anchorage (demo reel), 1996; 107509 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0155)
    - Paco Cao, "Rent A Body", Carol and Marylyn TV Talk Show, [1996]; 107508 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0466)
    - Pierrick Sorin, "A Very Full Life", et. al., [1996]; 107507 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0157)
    - Pierrick Sorin, "C'est Mignon toutsa", [1996]; 107506 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0143)
      Duration: [45 min.]
    - Susan Cianciolo, "Run 3 Fashion Show", 1996; 107505 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0679)
    - Adrianne Wortzel, "Technoseduction Exhibition", "My Robotic", "The Ship's Detective" projection installation, [1997]; 107504 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0159)
    - Ange Leccia, "Sabatina", 1997; 107503 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0410)
    - Brooklyn Bridge Anchorage - Rough Footage, 9/11/97, 1997; 107502 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0169)
    - Chrysanne Stathacos, "India 2026", "The Wish Machine", [1997]; 107501 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0683)
    - Magali Claude, "Tiems. Toi droit", "Les Gestes du Travail", "La Chora. Les rumours", 1997; 107500 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0490)
    - "ATM Art" (5/98), "Gesture as Value" (6/98), BBC [Press], 1998; 107499 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0303)
    - Ange Leccia, "ISA", 1998; 107498 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0379)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Detroit Techno, 1998; 107497 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0161)
    - Art in the Anchorage - Standard and Poor, "Big Night Out", 6/18/98, 1998; 107496 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0167)
    - Jerelyn Hanrahan, "Gesture as Value", [1998]; 107495 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0305)
    - Jeremy Dawson, Richard Gordon, Creative Time commercial loop, 11/2/98, 1998; 107494 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0389)
      Format: Beta
    - Jeremy Dawson, Richard Gordon, Creative Time commercial, 11/2/98, 1998; 107493 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0408)
    - Jeremy Dawson, Richard Gordon, Creative Time commercial loop, [1998]; 107492 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0387)
    - "Between Dreams and History" Installation Video Documentary, [1998]; 107491 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0665)
    - "Between Dreams and History", Installation Video (dir. Christopher Beaver), [1998]; 107490 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0530)
    - "Between Dreams and History", Rivington Show A, [1998]; 107489 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0613)
    - "Between Dreams and History", Rivington Show B, [1998]; 107488 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0612)
    - "Between Dreams and History", Ludlow Show Master, 1998; 107487 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0611)
    - "Between Dreams and History: The Making of Shimon Attie's Public Art Projects" (dir. Christopher Beaver), [1998]; 107486 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0666)
    - Shimon Attie, "Between Dreams and History", BBC, Fall 1998, 107485 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0532)
    - Shimon Attie, "Between Dreams and History" (installation version, dir. Christopher Beaver), [1998]; 107484 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0534)
    - The Art Guys with Todd Oldham, "Suits: The Clothes Make the Man", 11/2/98, 1998; 107483 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0572)
    - The Art Guys, Haverford '98, 1998; 107482 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0610)
    - The Art Guys, [1998]; 107481 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0578)
    - The Art Guys, CBS [Press], [1998]; 107480 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0582)
    - Theresa Duncan, Jeremy Blake, "History of Glamour", [1998]; 107479 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0676)
      Duration: [39 min.]
    - "F.R.E.D." Projections, Fall 1999 (shot by Roberto Guerra), 107478 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0624)
      Format: MiniDV
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Loud and Unhinged" (art video looped) 5/18/99, 1999; 107477 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0301)
      Duration: [120 min.]
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Loud and Unhinged" (fashion video looped) 5/18/99, 1999; 107476 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0297)
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Loud and Unhinged" (film video looped) 5/18/99, 1999; 107475 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0299)
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Loud and Unhinged", [1999]; 107474 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0125)
    - Courtney Harmel, Brooklyn Library Projections, 11/6/99 (Tape 1), 1999; 107473 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0193)
    - Kyong Park, "Architecture of Resistance", 1999; 107472 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0691)
    - Standard and Poor, Carpet Rollers, Park Restaurant, 2/2/99, 1999; 107471 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0249)
    - The Art Guys, Fashion TV [Press], 1999; 107470 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0580)
    - The 59th Minute - Genevieve Cadieux, "Portrait", 1999-2000; 107469 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0279)
    - [Art in the Anchorage] - Granular Synthesis, "Noise Gate" (Prod. Footage), [2000]; 107468 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0187)
    - "Tibor in Orbit", Times Square, May-June, 2000, 107467 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0275)
    - Bus Tour, 9/27/00, 2000; 107466 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0291)
    - Chris Doyle, "Leap", 2000; 107465 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0454)
    - Chris Doyle, "Leap", Apr 27-30, 2000, 107464 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0448)
    - Chris Doyle, "Leap" (Demo), [2000]; 107463 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0450)
    - "Leap", [2000]; 107462 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0514)
    - "Leap", Dec[ember], [2000]; 107461 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0452)
    - "Leap", Interviews, [2000]; 107460 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0456)
    - Kyong Park, "Detroit: Making it Better For You", 12/2000, 107459 (Box 32, Folder ID: 179.0692)
    - The 59th Minute - "Tibor in Orbit", 4/4/00, 2000; 107458 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0351)
    - "Leap", "Tribute in Light", "Tap", "59th Minute" (show reel), [2000-2002]; 107457 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0418)
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Honest", June 2001, 107456 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0123)
      TRT: [44 min.]
    - Art in the Anchorage - "Massless Medium: Explorations Sensory Immersion", 2001; 107455 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0171)
    - Art in Anchorage - Leo Villareal, "Building as Display", "Megaparticle", "Cloud Chamber (sound)", "Strobe Display", "Chase Display", [2001]; 107454 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0133)
      Duration: [11 min.]
    - Barry McGee, "Mass Destruction", Shibuya-Ku, Tokyo (Filmed by Cheryl Dunn), 2001; 107453 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0684)
    - Bonnen, Phillips, "Shaded Bandwidth's Proposal", [2001]; 107452 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0673)
      Duration: [7 min.]
    - Hans Haacke, May 12, 2001, 107451 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0245)
    - Mark Hansen, Ben Rubin, "Listening Post", 2001; 107450 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0661)
    - Mark Hansen, Ben Rubin, "Listening Post", 2001; 107449 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0662)
      Duration: [9 min.]
    - Music in the Anchorage - 6/21/01 (rough footage), 2001; 107448 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0646)
    - [Music in the Anchorage] - Porter Ricks, SND, 6/28 (#3), [2001]; 107447 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0618)
    - [Music in the Anchorage] - Porter Ricks, Thomas Heckman, 6/28 (#4), [2001]; 107446 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0620)
    - [Music in the Anchorage] 6/28 #3, [2001]; 107445 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0622)
    - Noam Toran, "Object for Lonely Men", Blur, 2001; 107444 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0558)
    - Rachel Stevens, NAAMP Portfolio Presentation, 12/01, 2001; 107443 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0428)
    - The 59th Minute - Bruce and Norman Yonemoto, "ahistory", Oct 19-Nov 30, 2001, 107442 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0347)
    - The 59th Minute - Gary Hill, Michael Snow, Mary Lucier, "Fast Forward", 12/2/2001-1/27/02, 107441 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0369)
    - The 59th Minute - Marco Brambilla, "Superstar", Feb 28-Apr 15, 2001, 107440 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0353)
    - The 59th Minute - Marco Brambilla, "Superstar"; Fischli and Weiss, "Cat Drinking Milk"; William Kentridge, "Shadow", 2001; 107439 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0257)
    - The 59th Minute - Michael Snow, "Fridge", 2001; 107438 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0478)
    - The 59th Minute - Fischli and Weiss, "Cat Drinking Milk"; William Kentridge, "Shadows"; Bruce and Norman Yonemoto, "ahistory"; Jeff Gibson, "Viralysis"; Gary Hill, "Liminal Object"; Mary Lucier, "Monarch"; Michael Snow, "Fridge"; Genevieve Cadieux, "Portrait", [2001]; 107437 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0480)
    - Vik Muniz, "What's The Big Idea" [EGG, The Arts Show], [2001]; 107436 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0678)
    - "Out of the Ashes", "Towers of Light", Dateline, 10/21/01 [Press], 2001; 107435 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0492)
    - "Out of the Ashes", Dateline, 10/21/01 [Press], 2001; 107434 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0287)
    - Memorials, CBS Evening News, 12/11/01 [Press], 2001; 107433 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0281)
    - "Tribute in Light" press conference, 3/6/02 (part 1 of 2) [Press], 2002; 107432 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0424)
    - "Tribute in Light", Anne Pasternak, Pure Oxygen, 3/12/02 [Press], 2002; 107431 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0550)
    - "Tribute in Light", Nippon Television, Tokyo, 3/9/02 [Press], 2002; 107430 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0422)
    - "Tribute in Light", Nippon Television, Tokyo, 3/9/02 [Press], 2002; 107429 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0546)
    - "Tribute in Light", Press Conference (tape 2 of 2) [Press], 2002; 107428 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0548)
    - "Tribute in Light", Pure Oxygen, 4/10/02 (Segment B) [Press], 2002; 107427 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0426)
    - "Tribute in Light", CNN, Towers of Light [Press], [2002]; 107426 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0544)
    - "Tribute in Light", Illumina TV, ArtsWorld [Press], [2002]; 107425 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0494)
    - "Tribute in Light", NY One [Press], [2002]; 107424 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0496)
    - "Tribute in Light", Towers of Light, Proun Space Studio, [2002]; 107423 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0498)
    - Therese Cafaro, Jayson Haedrich, "Tribute: A Documentary", [2002]; 107422 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0672)
      Duration: [27 min.]
    - Therese Cafaro, Jayson Haedrich, "Tribute: A Documentary", [2002]; 107421 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0420)
    - Everton Sylvester, Skylight Gallery, 9/5/02 (Tape 2), 2002; 107420 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0153)
    - Everton Sylvester, Skylight Gallery, 9/5/02 (Tape 4), 2002; 107419 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0165)
    - Everton Sylvester, 9/5/02 (tape 1), 2002; 107418 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0640)
    - Everton Sylvester, 9/5/02 (tape 3), 2002; 107417 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0630)
    - Gabri SI High School 9/13/02 (2 of 2), 2002; 107416 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0614)
    - Gabri SI High School, 9/13/02 (1 of 2), 2002; 107415 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0648)
    - Holiday Light Show - Grand Central Project, Comp Reel, [2002]; 107414 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0285)
    - James Buckhouse, Holly Brubach, "Tap" - Tech TV (30 second spot), 6/12/2002 [Press], 107413 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0283)
    - "Sonic Garden", NY Tonight [Press], [2002]; 107412 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0295)
    - Stephanie Simon, "Poster Project", 2/02, 2002; 107411 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0267)
    - The Kitchen and Creative Time - DHH Winless NY, 4/23/02, 2002; 107410 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0175)
      Duration: [56 min.]
    - Toshi, 8/28/02 (1 of 2), 2002; 107409 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0632)
    - Toshi, 8/28/02 (2 of 2), 2002; 107408 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0616)
    - William Wegman - [The 59th Minute] Fox Good Day Live, 11/18/02 [Press], 2002; 107407 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0373)
    - Adelle Lutz, "The Peace Piece", [2003]; 179.0604; 107406 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0604, E-records fales_mss179)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Original format: VHS, Duration: 00:04:00
    - Artist Roundtable (final group discussion), 8/5/03, 2003; 107405 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0135)
    - Artist Roundtable (Vardit's Group), 8/5/03, 2003; 107404 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0149)
    - Artists Roundtable, Vardit, [2003]; 107403 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0502)
    - Artist Roundtable, Carol's Group, 8/5/03, 2003; 107402 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0638)
    - Cai Guo-Qiang, "Gunpowder", drawings at Grucci, 8/7/03, 2003; 107401 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0634)
    - Cai Guo-Qiang, "Light Cycle", 2003; 107400 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0273)
    - [Cai Guo-Qiang], "Light Cycle", "Aerial", [2003]; 107399 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0189)
    - Cai Guo-Qiang, "Light Cycle", [2003]; 107398 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0636)
    - Focus Group, 3/24/03 (1 of 2), 2003; 107397 (Box not specified, Folder ID: 179.0642)
    - Focus Group, 3/24/03 (2 of 2), 2003; 107396 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0644)
    - The 59th Minute - Carlos Amorales, "The Forest", 2003; 107395 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0669)
    - The 59th Minute - William Wegman, "Dog Duet", 2003; 107394 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0401)
    - The 59th Minute - Thomas Struth, 2003; 107393 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0385)
    - [The 59th Minute] - Thomas Struth, "Video Portraits": Kim Heirston, Thomas Gutt, Anne Grefe, Rafael Hartmann, [2003]; 107392 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0606)
    - Thomas Struth Exhibit, German television, 2/4/03 [Press], 2003; 107391 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0361)
    - "Worst Possible Illusion: The Curiosity Cabinet of Vik Muniz", [2003]; 107390 (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0671)
      Duration: [5 min.]
    - CBS Sunday Morning, "Freedom of Expression", 7/4/04 [Press], 2004; 107389 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0293)
    - Freedom of Expression [Monument], 11/04, 2004; 107388 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0488)
    - Jenny Holzer, "For New York City" (1), 2004; 107387 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0584)
    - Jenny Holzer, "For New York City" (2), 2004; 107386 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0592)
    - Jenny Holzer, "For The City" (raw footage), [2004]; 107385 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0586)
    - "For New York City", '04, Xenon Projections at Bethesda Fountain, Central Park, 10/2704 (tape 4), 2004; 107384 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0590)
    - O and A [Sam Auinger and Bruce Odland], "Blue Moon", Stephanie Simon 5/04 [Press], 2004; 107383 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0470)
    - The 59th Minute - "Dream Sequence", "Dwelling", "Mousetrap", 1/18/04, 2004; 107382 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0307)
    - The 59th Minute - Carlos Amorales, "The Forest", 10/28/04, 2004; 107381 (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0309)
    - The 59th Minute - Gunther Selichar, [2004]; 107380 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0247)
    - The 59th Minute - Hiraki Sawa, "Dwelling"; Janaina Tschape, "Dream Sequence", Jan 21-May 16, 2004, 107379 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0377)
    - The 59th Minute - Hiraki Sawa, "Dwelling"; Janaina Tschape, "Dream Sequence", Jan 21-May 16, 2004, 107378 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0414)
    - The 59th Minute - [Carlos] Amorales, Televisa New York, [2004-2005]; 107377 (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0482)
    - Anne Pasternak, Stephanie Simon, 2/05 [Press], 2005; 107376 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0269)
    - Dreamland Artist Club - Stephanie Simon, 2005; 107375 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0129)
    - Jenny Holzer, Bobst Library, NYU, 11/16/05, 2005; 107374 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0588)
    - Jenny Holzer, Political Art (edit), Reuters, Fall 2005, 107373 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0594)